[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Under what Austin bridge would you find the largest urban bat population in North America?",
    "options": [
      "George W. Bush Shoal Creek Bridge",
      "Loop 360 Pennybacker Bridge",
      "Willie Hugh Nelson Lake Austin Bridge",
      "Ann W. Richards Congress Avenue Bridge"
    ],
    "answer": "Ann W. Richards Congress Avenue Bridge"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "For what Austin, Texas landmark has the Louisiana State Capitol building been used as a film stand-in?",
    "options": [
      "Blanton Museum of Art",
      "The Texas State Capitol Building",
      "The University of Texas Tower",
      "The LBJ Library"
    ],
    "answer": "The University of Texas Tower"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following choices is NOT true about the local laws in Austin, Texas?",
    "options": [
      "It is legal for any male over age 21 with a clear criminal history to carry concealed handguns.",
      "It is legal for women to appear topless in public.",
      "It is illegal to shoot a buffalo from a second story hotel window.",
      "Both paper and plastic disposable bags are banned at all retail stores."
    ],
    "answer": "It is legal for any male over age 21 with a clear criminal history to carry concealed handguns."
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "According to Forbes, between 2004 and 2014 Austin, Texas had the largest growth of jobs in the country in what field?",
    "options": [
      "Agricultural",
      "Entertainment",
      "Information Technology",
      "Education"
    ],
    "answer": "Information Technology"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is the name of the lake created in downtown Austin, Texas by dams on the Colorado River?",
    "options": [
      "Town Lake",
      "Lady Bird Lake",
      "Lake Austin",
      "Lake LBJ"
    ],
    "answer": "Lady Bird Lake"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Select the name of the central Austin, Texas park that hosts the annual Christmas Trail of Lights and Barton Springs Pool.",
    "options": [
      "Emma Long Metropolitan Park",
      "Walnut Creek Metropolitan Park",
      "Zilker Metropolitan Park",
      "Barton Creek Greenbelt"
    ],
    "answer": "Zilker Metropolitan Park"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Name the popular children's story and cartoon character who has an annual birthday party in Austin, Texas.",
    "options": [
      "Felix the Cat",
      "Gumby",
      "Eeyore",
      "Woody Woodpecker"
    ],
    "answer": "Eeyore"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "For which events would you visit Zilker Park in Austin, Texas?",
    "options": [
      "Willie Nelson's 4th of July Picnic, Carnaval Brasilieiro, Armadillo Christmas Bazaar",
      "Austin City Limits Music Festival, Zilker Kite Festival, Blues on the Green",
      "Old Settlers Music Festival, Star of Texas Fair and Rodeo, Batfest",
      "Old Pecan Street Arts Festival, O. Henry Pun-Off, Austin Reggae Festival"
    ],
    "answer": "Austin City Limits Music Festival, Zilker Kite Festival, Blues on the Green"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "On 22 November 1963, US President John F. Kennedy was assassinated in Dallas, Texas. At what Austin, Texas landmark was he scheduled to appear later on the same date?",
    "options": [
      "Municipal Auditorium",
      "Paramount Theater",
      "Long Center for the Performing Arts",
      "Bass Concert Hall"
    ],
    "answer": "Municipal Auditorium"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Esther's Follies has been a well-known landmark in downtown Austin, Texas since 1977. What is Esther's Follies?",
    "options": [
      "A nickname for the Austin Police Department headquarters building",
      "A dance club for women only",
      "A comedy house featuring music, magic, and short skits",
      "A restaurant and bar featuring big band and swing music"
    ],
    "answer": "A comedy house featuring music, magic, and short skits"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Which is the following is a nickname of Austin?",
    "options": [
      "Rodeo Capital of North America",
      "Live Music Capital of the World",
      "RV Capital of the World",
      "Home of the Candy Dance"
    ],
    "answer": "Live Music Capital of the World"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What is a favorite cooling-off spot where you can take a dip without leaving the city?",
    "options": [
      "The Greenbelt",
      "Barton Springs Pool",
      "McKinney Falls State Park",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "When was Austin founded?",
    "options": [
      "1839",
      "1943",
      "1795",
      "1900"
    ],
    "answer": "1839"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Austin hosts an annual fun-raiser, or should that be fund-raiser? in the guise of a birthday party for which A. A. Milne character?",
    "options": [
      "Eeyore",
      "Tigger",
      "Pooh",
      "Piglet"
    ],
    "answer": "Eeyore"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What was Austin originally called?",
    "options": [
      "Coupon",
      "Waterloo",
      "Dogtown",
      "Experiment"
    ],
    "answer": "Waterloo"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What spring in Austin is considered the fourth largest spring in Texas?",
    "options": [
      "Hamilton Pool",
      "Deep Eddy",
      "Barton Springs",
      "Krause Springs"
    ],
    "answer": "Barton Springs"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What was Austin’s first municipal airport named?",
    "options": [
      "Eek Airport",
      "Austin-Bergstrom International Airport",
      "Moron Airport",
      "Mueller Airport"
    ],
    "answer": "Mueller Airport"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What is another name that Austin, Texas, is known by?",
    "options": [
      "Rodeo Capital of North America",
      "Live Music Capital of the World",
      "The Adam’s Rib of Barbecue",
      "Silicon Hills"
    ],
    "answer": "Live Music Capital of the World"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "How many students attend the University of Texas located in Austin?",
    "options": [
      "50000",
      "36000",
      "100000",
      "75000"
    ],
    "answer": "50000"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What is the mascot for the University of Texas at Austin?",
    "options": [
      "Longhorn",
      "Bull",
      "Mustang",
      "Cowboy"
    ],
    "answer": "Longhorn"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "When was the University of Texas at Austin founded?",
    "options": [
      "1839",
      "1883",
      "1901",
      "1920"
    ],
    "answer": "1883"
  }
]